ukecigstore.com 2019-09-17

# Privacy Policy — UK ECIG STORE

This privacy notice tells you about the information we collect from you when you use our website. In collecting this information, we are acting as a data controller and, by law, we are required to provide you with information about us, about why and how we use your data, and about the rights you have over your data.

When you are using the UK ECIG STORE website, UK Electronic Cigarette Limited (Company number 08090491) is the data controller.

  * Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

    * Information that you provide to us in your dealings with us. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our services or requesting further services and/or information from us.
    * We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our site.
    * Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfillment of your orders.
    * Details we receive from credit reference and fraud detection agencies.
    * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and the resources that you access.
    * Please see our full privacy policy and terms of use at http://www.ukecigstore.com/termsandconditions for further details.

  * Who we are

We are UK Electronic Cigarette Limited (trading as UK ECIG STORE). Our address is Fourth Floor, York House, Empire Way, Wembley, HA9 0PA. You can contact us by post at the above address, by email at [dpo@ukecigstore.com](mailto:dpo@ukecigstore.com) or by telephone on +44 (0)20 3475 4885

  * When you use our website

When you use our website to browse our products and services and view the information we make available, a number of cookies are used by us and by third parties to allow the website to function, to collect useful information about visitors and to help to make your user experience better.

Some of the cookies we use are strictly necessary for our website to function, and we don’t ask for your consent to place these on your computer. For further information, please visit the cookies section on this page.

  * When you submit an enquiry via our website

When you submit an enquiry via our website, we ask you for your name, contact telephone number and email address.

We use this information to respond to your query, including providing you with any requested information about our products and services. We may also email you several times after your enquiry in order to follow up on your interest and ensure that we have answered your it to your satisfaction. We will do this based on our legitimate interest in providing accurate information prior to a sale.

Your enquiry is stored and processed as an email which is hosted by Google within the European Economic Area (EEA). It is also logged on a CRM system on a cloud server based in the European Economic Area (EEA).

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

We keep enquiry emails for five years, after which they are securely archived and kept for ten years, when we delete them. CRM records are kept for five years after the last contact with you.

  * When you purchase a product from our website

When you purchase products from us online, we ask you for your name, billing/delivery address, date of birth, contact telephone number and email address. We also record your IP (Internet Protocol) address, which is the address of your computer on the Internet.

We will use your information to complete your purchase, process your order and to send you your products. We will also send you a receipt via email and we may use your telephone number to contact you regarding your purchase.

We require this information in order to process your order, deliver your products and fulfil our contract with you. We record your IP address in order to show that the correct tax was applied to the sale, which we are required to do by law.

Your information is stored on our website and on our cloud server, both of which are based within the European Union. Your credit card details are passed to a third-party payment processor which is based in the USA and is certified to the EU-US Privacy Shield (which requires effective safeguards for your information). We do not retain your credit/debit card information.

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you. We keep your order information for an indefinite period.

  * When you sign up to receive our newsletter

When you sign up to receive our newsletter, we ask for your name and your email address.

We will ask for your consent to use your name and email address to email you our newsletter which contains information about our products and other information which we feel might be of interest to you.

You can withdraw your consent at any time and we will stop sending you the newsletter.

Your name and email address are shared with a third party mailing system. This company has contractually committed to providing appropriate safeguards for your personal data which means it will be protected in l ine with the legal requirements of the European Union.

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

We keep your personal data for as long as we produce and distribute our newsletter. If you withdraw your consent, we will mark your details so that they are not used and delete them after two years.

  * When you submit a website review

When you submit a review about us we record your name, your email address and your IP (Internet Protocol) address, which is the address of your computer on the Internet.

We use this information to provide verified independent views about our products to potential customers. Your name and the content of your review (but not your email address or IP address) may be publicly displayed on our website. We will do this based on our legitimate interest in marketing our products and services.

Your details are shared with a third party reviews system which is based within the European Economic Area (EEA).

We do not use the information you provide to make any automated decisions that might affect you.

Your personal data is stored for as long as we are marketing the product or services that the review refers to, after which it is deleted. You may ask us to remove your review at any time.

  * Your rights as a data subject

By law, you can ask us what information we hold about you, and you can ask us to correct it if it is inaccurate. If we have asked for your consent to process your personal data, you may withdraw that consent at any time.

If we are processing your personal data for reasons of consent or to fulfil a contract, you can ask us to give you a copy of the information in a machine-readable format so that you can transfer it to another provider.

If we are processing your personal data for reasons of consent or legitimate interest, you can request that your data be erased.

You have the right to ask us to stop using your information for a period of time if you believe we are not doing so lawfully.

Finally, in some circumstances you can ask us not to reach decisions affecting you using automated processing or profiling.

To submit a request regarding your personal data by email, post or telephone, please use the contact information provided above in the ‘Who we are’ section of this policy.

  * Cookies

When you use our website to browse our products and services and view the information we make available, a number of cookies are used by us and by third parties to allow the website to function, to collect useful information about visitors and to help to make your user experience better.

Some of the cookies we use are strictly necessary for our website to function, and we don’t ask for your consent to place these on your computer. These cookies are shown below.

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
popupdata

| 

Used by Magento to show welcome message. Collects number of visits.  
  
Currency

| 

Holds the relevant currency to the country you are browsing from, and for this it identifies the location of the visitor.  
  
CART

| 

The association with the customer's shopping cart.  
  
CUSTOMER

| 

An encrypted version of the shopper's customer ID.  
  
CUSTOMER_INFO

| 

An encrypted version of the shopper's customer group.  
  
FRONTEND

| 

The customer's session ID.  
  
GUEST-VIEW

| 

Determines if guests can edit their orders.  
  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART

| 

A link to information about the shopper's cart and viewing history.  
  
STORE

| 

The store view or language chosen by the shopper.  
  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS

| 

The products recently viewed by the shopper.  
  
WISHLIST

| 

An encrypted list of products added to the shopper's wishlist.  
  
WISHLIST_CNT

| 

The number of items in the shopper's wishlist.  
  
_utmb

| 

Determines new sessions/visits.  
  
_utmc

| 

Determines if the shopper is in a new session/visit.  
  
As well as the cookies we use, various third parties.These are shown below.

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
Ometria

| 

This software helps us collect and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, response to marketing activity, shopping times, email address and IP address. That information helps us to improve the website and your shopping experience, and to make our marketing campaigns relevant  
  
_utmz and _utma

| 

These cookies enable the function of Google Analytics. Software. Like Ometria, this software helps us collect and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, response to marketing activity and shopping times. That information helps us to improve the website and your shopping experience, and to make our marketing campaigns relevant.

The data stored by these cookies can be seen only by the relevant teams at UK Ecig Store and Google and never shows any confidential information.  
  
uslk_s, uslk_e

| 

For user identification. Contains a user ID, the name of the end user, email address, and number of visits. Used by Google Analytics.  
  
traffic_src

| 

Used by Google Analytics to identify how the user arrived to the website.  
  
_gid

| 

Used by Google Analytics to store user ID and marketing campaign ID.  
  
_ga

| 

Stores user ID.  
  
_unam

| 

Used by Share This service to monitor click activity. Navigation history, time spent on each page. Only works if a user is signed into their Share This account.  
  
intercom-id-zmcdradn

| 

Collects the user email.  
  
hubspotutk

| 

The HubSpot Analytics system identifies unique records using two pieces of data, the usertoken (stored in the visitors browser in the hubspotutk cookie) and the email address.  
  
  * Your right to complain

If you have a complaint about our use of your information, we would prefer you to contact us directly in the first instance so that we can address your complaint. However, you can also contact the Information Commissioner’s Office via their website at [www.ico.org.uk/concerns](http://www.ico.org.uk/concerns)

  * Updates to this privacy policy

We regularly review and, if appropriate, update this privacy policy from time to time, and as our services and use of personal data evolves. If we want to make use of your personal data in a way that we haven’t previously identified, we will contact you to provide information about this and, if necessary, to ask for your consent.
